[{"answer": "Well, it was clearly over the top.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "What's your reaction?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Look, there's a reason.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "-- all this is getting completely out of hand?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Thirty-eight percent, major restrictions.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "You said 38 percent?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Because politicians underrate the intelligence and the reasonableness of the American people.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Why is nobody saying anything in any sort of leadership way?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "If we outlaw those malleable bullet magazines the fella Holmes could have -- in the first minute when he killed most of the people, he would have had to reload six times.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Why bring laws in about anything?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "I think I'd choose Condoleezza Rice because I think he's got some weaknesses in foreign affairs which he's demonstrated.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Governor Rendell?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Well, just because I felt that, you know, I was asked to carry the water and carry a message during this election, and to make social -- a socialist solutions part of the narrative of this election, because they're being left out, and they work.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Why have you decided to get engaged properly?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "That's just what happens when you make everything for sale.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Why has it come to this?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Well, I would -- I would ask the richest among us, the richest corporate citizens to, you know, include the American people in their jobs.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "How would you get Americans back to work?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, I just wanted to say that a large part of my solution is to, as FDR did, write down the principal on the debt.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Yes, Roseanne?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "How was it for you?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Properly in love?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "I'm getting more, you know, the issue of mental health is very near and dear to me and as I go on and, you know, as I pull it in and synthesize and do all the things.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Roseanne, you calming down a little bit?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Well, there's more than one, Piers.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "And if I was to pin you down and say right, apart from any relationship or children in your life, if you could relive one moment again of your entire life career, whatever, what moment would you choose?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "I've flown with my dad a number of times, yes.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "You guys fly often together?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "It was crazy.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "What goes through your mind?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it never crossed my mind until we started going down and then at that point there you think -- you think to yourself, this might be the last -- this might be the last evidence or the last time we get -- that our family gets to see us.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "But did you think as you were videotaping you might be videoing your own deaths here?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "He's actually doing really well.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "How is he now?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "No, not initially.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "I was going to say, did you realize that the whole thing was being caught on camera?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "It's been a skill I've developed over the years.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "You've always been quick at the draw?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "Yes, I think people once they get to mow me and realize I'm not that dangerous off the court.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "Boyfriends been able to deal with the rattlesnake hands?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "Well, I think I'm really blessed and privileged right now to be on some great teams.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "How do you feel about being right now pound for pound the best female basketball player in the world?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "It absolutely does.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "That brings with it a special kind of pressure, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Losing is a necessary part of sports.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "How do you deal with losing?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "Well, there are not many people in the basketball world or the sports world.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "What does Michael Jordan mean to you?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "Well, of course, winning that gold medal is first, but after I want to continue to compete as long as I can as a professional athlete.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "What is your ambition for you after the Olympics?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "Well, she was very moved.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "Why did your mom choose that?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "I hope so.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "She would be pretty proud I think at how you turned out?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Well, to start with, my father-in-law was murdered in 1996 and I found his body and I rarely relate to people who have had a huge loss like that.", "docId": "120809pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "Explain to me what motivated you to start with?", "qSentId": 656}]